<library path="lib/libbehaviors">
  <class name="behaviors/pac-man-bot/init" 
         type="behaviors::pac_man_behs::init" 
         base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
  <description>
    The first state in the pac-man-bot statemachine.
    This behavior will control two 
    things. First, it will control the switch waiting
    period. This state will initialize on startup, and
    wait for the start switch to be pressed. Secondly,
    it will wait 30 seconds during the communication
    phase. After both of these are completed, it will
    release control.
  </description>
  </class>

  <class name="behaviors/pac-man-bot/check_for_ghosts" 
         type="behaviors::pac_man_behs::check_for_ghosts" 
         base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
  <description>
    This is the second state within the pac-man-bot sm.
    It checks where the ghosts are publishes that out to
    all the states that need it.
  </description>
  </class>

  <class name="behaviors/pac-man-bot/ground_search" 
         type="behaviors::pac_man_behs::ground_search" 
         base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
  <description>
    ground search will perform the search in the two 
    boxes f and h. This will have a small internal 
    state machine:
    - move to start
        - moves to the starting point for the search
    - search
        - slowly moves down the wall
        - exists when at the bottom
    grab block
        - if a block is found during the search, then
            grab it
        - returns to last point in search
  </description>
  </class>

  <class name="behaviors/pac-man-bot/reach_search" 
         type="behaviors::pac_man_behs::reach_search" 
         base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
  <description>
    This class is used to search over the walls in 
    the pac-man-bot arena. To do this, we will take in
    the distance sent from the arm to monitor when an 
    block passes from underneath it to grab.

    This also inherits from ground_search because there
    were a lot of similarities between the two. Bc of 
    this, it has the same fsm as class.
  </description>
  </class>

  <class name="behaviors/pac-man-bot/attack_ghosts" 
         type="behaviors::pac_man_behs::attack_ghosts" 
         base_class_type="nodelet::Nodelet">
  <description>
    The attach ghosts state attacks ghosts(duh). It 
    will listen to the ghost location topic and 
    when it is transitioned into, it will navigate to
    both ghosts that are sent to it at the beginning.
    This also has a timer in it to keep track of the 
    power period. If the timer ends, it gives up
    control
  </description>
  </class>
</library>